let STORE = [
  {
    question: "What Detroit Tigers pitcher did David Ortiz hit a grand slam off of in Game 2 of the 2013 American League Championship Series?",

    answers: ["Joaquin Benoit", "Justin Verlander", "Max Scherzer", "Anibal Sanchez"],

    correct: "Joaquin Benoit"
  },

    {
    question: "How many Red Sox players have won the batting Triple Crown?",

    answers: ["1", "2", "3", "None, nice try"],

    correct: "2"
  },

    {
    question: "What year was Babe Ruth traded to the New York Yankees?",

    answers: ["1917", "1918", "1919", "1920"],

    correct: "1919"
  },

    {
    question: "Furthermore, how long did the Curse of the Bambino hang over the Red Sox?",

    answers: ["82 years", "86 years", "88 years", "92 years"],

    correct: "86 years"
  },

    {
    question: "What inning did Tim Wakefield give up a walk-off home run to the Yankee's Aaron Boone in the 2003 American League Championship Series?",

    answers: ["9th", "10th", "11th", "12th"],

    correct: "11th"
  },

    {
    question: "Who was the 2004 World Series MVP?",

    answers: ["Johnny Damon", "Manny Ramirez", "David Ortiz", "Curt Schilling"],

    correct: "Manny Ramirez"
  },

    {
    question: "What Red Sox player waved a walk-off home run fair in Game 6 of the 1975 World Series?",

    answers: ["Ted Williams", "Carl Yastrzemski", "Jim Rice", "Carlton Fisk"],

    correct: "Carlton Fisk"
  },

    {
    question: "Who did the Red Sox defeat in the 2007 World Series?",

    answers: ["The St. Louis Cardinals", "The Colorado Rockies", "The San Francisco Giants", "The Philadelphia Phillies"],

    correct: "The Colorado Rockies"
  },

    {
    question: "What Red Sox player made his major league debut by hitting a grand slam?",

    answers: ["Daniel Nava", "Dustin Pedroia", "Ryan Kalish", "Jacoby Ellsbury"],

    correct: "Daniel Nava"
  },
    {
    question: "How many World Series have the Red Sox won?",

    answers: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],

    correct: "8"
  }
]